



# PERSONAL INFO

#### phone

+36 20 388 8827

#### email

hello@tengerbori.hu

#### website

http://www.tengerbori.hu

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/boritenger/

#### Behance

https://www.behance.net/borimoon

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

wireframing
visual design
prototyping
front-end design

SOFT SKILLS

user empathy

client relations

communication

self-motivation

# BIO

I'm a designer who excels in all aspects of UI design. I have many years of history creating visuals for both physical and online products.

Currently, I'm focusing on creating user interfaces. I natively speak HTML, CSS, and also gained some valuable knowledge of JavaScript. My skills and learnings allow me to bring ideas from concept to prototypes and then to production.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### **UI** Designer

OPPI | Oct 2017 - present

Currently, I collaborate with a freelance team named Oppi. I work on digital projects from smart hotel user interfaces to website design and development.

### Designer

WINKLER & STENZEL | Oct 2011 - Apr 2018

I worked on both print and digital products. I participated in several advertising campaigns, branding, and rebranding projects. I designed and developed websites and product landing pages for our clients.

# **Graphic Designer**

ART-VERSIO ADVERTISING AGENCY | Mar 2010 - Oct 2011

## Lecturer

ÓBUDA UNIVERSITY REJTŐ SÁNDOR FACULTY | Sep 2009 - Dec 2009

# **EDUCATION**

## **Front-end Development**

MOME CODE | 2015

# **Bachelor's Degree Print and Multimedia**

ÓBUDA UNIVERSITY REJTŐ SÁNDOR FACULTY | 2009

### **Graphic Design**

ART SCHOOL OF BUDA | 2004